<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-22T14:36:47+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Tifra Yanis</title><entry><title type="html">Machida</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/blog/Machida" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Machida" /><published>2018-09-20T10:10:01+02:00</published><updated>2018-09-20T10:10:01+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/blog/Machida</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/blog/Machida">&lt;body&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Presentation &lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
                &lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt; 
                    &lt;p&gt;The population of Machida (町田市) is estimated at 429,040 inhabitants for an area of ​​71.63 km2. As I said earlier this city was one of my main destination in the beginning because ot was only 2 station far from my university. Indeed, this city offers a lots of stores, shops, animation and is also a very crowded transit because of the Odakyu line which allows people to go to Shinjuku which is the biggest station and one of the most famous district of Japan.&lt;/p&gt; 
                    &lt;p&gt;More than a hub Machida has also a lot of people stopping there for work and like me many foreigner. Indeed, this fact is probably because two main universities are nearby : Aoyama Gakuin and J. F. Oberlin. These both university welcome (more ans more) many exchange students every semester.&lt;/p&gt;                                                               
                &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
                &lt;figure&gt;  
                   &lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/intro.jpg&quot; class=&quot;page_machi feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;picture of machida&quot; /&gt;
                   &lt;figcaption id=&quot;center_cap&quot;&gt;Picture of the main avenue in machida&lt;/figcaption&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;h2 style=&quot;text-align: right;&quot;&gt;My personal food recommendation &lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
                &lt;div class=&quot;col-2&quot;&gt;
                    &lt;video id=&quot;season_dining&quot; class=&quot;feature_item_style&quot; controls=&quot;controls&quot; preload=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;source src=&quot;../images/post/machida/season_dining.MP4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;                
                        &lt;source src=&quot;../images/post/machida/backup.webm&quot; /&gt;
                        Your browser does not support the video tag.
                    &lt;/video&gt;  
                &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;div class=&quot;col-10&quot;&gt; 
                    &lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt; 
                        &lt;p&gt;One of the place I have been the most is the Season Dining. This place is in the building when you leave the station in front of you. I discovered this place first when I was going to play soccer on the rooftop, and I noticed immediately because of for the concept. Indeed, all the floor is divided in restaurant with all having their speciality. Indian, Vietnamese (definitely my favorite), Okonomiyaki ... The choice is really big and prices are correct, even tho I would not eat there everyday. &lt;/p&gt; 
                        &lt;p&gt;This information leads to my conclusion of this place, except this place I have been you can of course find all the famous chains (sukiya,Mcdonald,Wendy's...), which are really affordable for a good taste. I would definitely recommend they Cheese Gyudon, as a french of course this was my favorite (チーズ牛丼)&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p&gt;To get a drink or enjoy a night with friends, I can give you two advice. First, the most casual one again is going to the famous chains (pictures below) like DomaDoma 土間土間, Torikizoku 鳥貴族...).&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;figure&gt;  
                         &lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/rue.JPG&quot; class=&quot;page_arti feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;figure of machida&quot; /&gt; 
                        &lt;/figure&gt; 
                        &lt;p&gt;These famous places provide a good compromise between affordable price and good quality of foods drinks. But again, I advice to try them all to get a better idea or get a better understanding of each identity and offers, such that Torikizoku for the Yakitori. Famous Izakaya chain are also really good because of their english menu, so their accessibility as a foreigner will be way more simple compare to traditional restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p&gt;However, don't get me wrong you will be very lucky if they have one or one of the staff actually can speak a little english. I would recommend if it's your first time in this kind of place to go with a japanese speaker in order to get a better understanding of the course plan in a Izakaya (飲み放題と食べ放題&lt;/p&gt;  
                        &lt;p&gt;Second, when the time has come where you finally got enough of the famous Izakaya, my second advice is to let you charm by the city. Indeed, for me one of the most important quality of the city is that the center is really small.&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p&gt;Every places are not too far from each other so you can try all the roads by walking and enjoy the view. &lt;/p&gt;                                                                  
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;During some of my night adventures I discovered a lot of traditional places, independant restaurant, even chicha's. It's also at night that you can enjoy a different point of view and another side of the city. Like every city in Japan, girl's bar and nightclub(one) and all of the night life is very developed and active, but I never get into these places so I cannot provide any details or information about it. &lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;To conclude all of these experiences and adventures made me fall in love with this city I hope you can visit it one day too. Feel free to check the official website of some of the restaurant I mention in this article !&lt;/p&gt;                
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
              &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6 cent&quot;&gt;
                    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.doma-doma.com/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/domadoma.png&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.matsuyafoods.co.jp/english/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/matsuya.jpeg&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;http://wendys.co.jp/store/collabo.html&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/wendys.jpeg&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mcdonalds.co.jp/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/mcdonald.png&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt; 
            &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6 cent&quot;&gt;
                    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shirokiya.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/shirokiya.jpg&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.watami.vn/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/watami.jpg&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torikizoku.co.jp/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/torikizoku.png&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-3&quot;&gt;
                            &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sukiya.jp/en/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/post/machida/sukiya.png&quot; class=&quot;logo feature_item img-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Presentation The population of Machida (町田市) is estimated at 429,040 inhabitants for an area of ​​71.63 km2. As I said earlier this city was one of my main destination in the beginning because ot was only 2 station far from my university. Indeed, this city offers a lots of stores, shops, animation and is also a very crowded transit because of the Odakyu line which allows people to go to Shinjuku which is the biggest station and one of the most famous district of Japan. More than a hub Machida has also a lot of people stopping there for work and like me many foreigner. Indeed, this fact is probably because two main universities are nearby : Aoyama Gakuin and J. F. Oberlin. These both university welcome (more ans more) many exchange students every semester. Picture of the main avenue in machida My personal food recommendation Your browser does not support the video tag. One of the place I have been the most is the Season Dining. This place is in the building when you leave the station in front of you. I discovered this place first when I was going to play soccer on the rooftop, and I noticed immediately because of for the concept. Indeed, all the floor is divided in restaurant with all having their speciality. Indian, Vietnamese (definitely my favorite), Okonomiyaki ... The choice is really big and prices are correct, even tho I would not eat there everyday. This information leads to my conclusion of this place, except this place I have been you can of course find all the famous chains (sukiya,Mcdonald,Wendy's...), which are really affordable for a good taste. I would definitely recommend they Cheese Gyudon, as a french of course this was my favorite (チーズ牛丼) To get a drink or enjoy a night with friends, I can give you two advice. First, the most casual one again is going to the famous chains (pictures below) like DomaDoma 土間土間, Torikizoku 鳥貴族...). These famous places provide a good compromise between affordable price and good quality of foods drinks. But again, I advice to try them all to get a better idea or get a better understanding of each identity and offers, such that Torikizoku for the Yakitori. Famous Izakaya chain are also really good because of their english menu, so their accessibility as a foreigner will be way more simple compare to traditional restaurant. However, don't get me wrong you will be very lucky if they have one or one of the staff actually can speak a little english. I would recommend if it's your first time in this kind of place to go with a japanese speaker in order to get a better understanding of the course plan in a Izakaya (飲み放題と食べ放題 Second, when the time has come where you finally got enough of the famous Izakaya, my second advice is to let you charm by the city. Indeed, for me one of the most important quality of the city is that the center is really small. Every places are not too far from each other so you can try all the roads by walking and enjoy the view. During some of my night adventures I discovered a lot of traditional places, independant restaurant, even chicha's. It's also at night that you can enjoy a different point of view and another side of the city. Like every city in Japan, girl's bar and nightclub(one) and all of the night life is very developed and active, but I never get into these places so I cannot provide any details or information about it. To conclude all of these experiences and adventures made me fall in love with this city I hope you can visit it one day too. Feel free to check the official website of some of the restaurant I mention in this article !</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/post/machida/machida.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/post/machida/machida.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Arrival in Japan</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/blog/Arrival-in-japan" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arrival in Japan" /><published>2018-09-04T10:10:01+02:00</published><updated>2018-09-04T10:10:01+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/blog/Arrival-in-japan</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/blog/Arrival-in-japan">&lt;body&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;parallax&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;txtparallax&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Landing&lt;/h2&gt;
    When I arrive in Japan I was totally lost. Indeed, the fist step was to get my visa validated and the reach the group of student that were going to my university. At this point it was very difficult to discover the Japanese writting system, Kanji's, Hiragana and Katakana  were all surrounding us. Except the lost of my luggage by my flight company I grabbed my bust ticket.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;parallax2&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;txtparallax&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Bus Time !&lt;/h2&gt;
    On my way from Narita to MAchida (3h30 on bus) I took advantage of the travelling time to rest a little from the long flight and enjoy the view of the Japanese highways and mainly rural landscape
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;parallax3&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;txtparallax&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Arrival in the dormitory&lt;/h2&gt;
   Our bus finally reach Machida which is the closest stop from Aoyama Gakuin University 青山学院大学(Sagamihara Campus) but we will discover the secrets of this city in another chapter ;).  To conclude this chapter, I just install myself in the dorm and start to be familiar with the train system in japan after starting my exchange student orientation Program plannned by my university.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Landing When I arrive in Japan I was totally lost. Indeed, the fist step was to get my visa validated and the reach the group of student that were going to my university. At this point it was very difficult to discover the Japanese writting system, Kanji's, Hiragana and Katakana were all surrounding us. Except the lost of my luggage by my flight company I grabbed my bust ticket. Bus Time ! On my way from Narita to MAchida (3h30 on bus) I took advantage of the travelling time to rest a little from the long flight and enjoy the view of the Japanese highways and mainly rural landscape Arrival in the dormitory Our bus finally reach Machida which is the closest stop from Aoyama Gakuin University 青山学院大学(Sagamihara Campus) but we will discover the secrets of this city in another chapter ;). To conclude this chapter, I just install myself in the dorm and start to be familiar with the train system in japan after starting my exchange student orientation Program plannned by my university.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/post/arrival/arrival.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/TifraYanis/post/arrival/arrival.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>